

Gonzalo, TERZANO

Web Developer
26 Years
Córdoba, Argentina
Mobile: +549 0264 154649709
E-mail: gonzaloterzano@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Hello! I'm Gonzalo Terzano. Semi-Senior Web Developer, with 2-3 years of experience in this area. I've skills to work in a team and individually. In order to achieve excellent results in the tasks assigned I always offer my best effort and dedication.

EXPERIENCE

February 2016 – Present Globant Cordoba, Argentina

Position: Web UI Developer

Working in a busy team sometimes under pressure. Always making projects of eLearning, mostly using AngularJS, but also using HTML5 and Phaser (JS Framework) in some projects for create friendly & interactive environments.

April 2015 – January 2016 TravelPAQ San Juan, Argentina

Position: Web UI Developer & Backend Developer

Worked in a great team, developing an important system for the tourism area that improving the interaction between wholesalers and online sellers. CakePHP and AngularJS were used for develop this project.

April 2010 – January 2016 UNSJ, FCEFyN San Juan, Argentina

Position: Teaching assistant

Worked in six different subjects, assisting in practical classes, even giving class in some particular cases.

SKILLS

- ✓ AngularJS
- ✓ JQuery
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ KnockoutJS
- ✓ HTML5
- ✓ CSS3

- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ CakePHP
- ✓ Git
- ✓ Gulp
- ✓ NodeJS
- ✓ PHP

- ✓ C#
- ✓ C
- ✓ SourceTree
- ✓ Photoshop

EDUCATION

2009 - Present

San Juan - Argentina

"Degree in Computer Science"

UNSJ – Fac. Cs. Exactas F. y N., without

preseting the Thesis.

GPA: 8.6 of 10

2005 - 2008 San Juan - Argentina

"Electronics Technician"

UNSJ - Esc Industrial D. F. Sarmiento

GPA: 8.57 of 10

LENGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Conversational level